我叫做约翰·菲茨杰拉德·拜尔斯
My name is John Fitzgerald Byers.
是与我们第35任总统同名
I was named after our 35th president.
我不断重复着这样一个美丽的梦
And I keep having this beautiful dream.
在我的梦里 1963年11月22日的事情
In my dream, the events of November 22, 1 963...
从来没发生过
never happened.
在梦里 与我同名的总统也从来没有遇刺
In it, my namesake was never assassinated.
我梦中的其它事情也与现实不同
Other things are different too in my dream.
我的国家充满希望与纯真
My country is hopeful and innocent,
再度年轻 精神上年轻
young again, young in spirit.
我的同胞信任他们选出的官员
My fellow citizens trust their elected officials,
从来没有被官员出卖过
never once having been betrayed by them.
我的政府真的是人民组成
My government is truly of the people,
由人民选出 为人民服务
by the people, for the people.
我对于国家和自己的一切希望
All my hopes for my country, for myself
全都获得了满足
all are fulfilled.
我拥有一个人能拥有的一切
I have everything a person could want
房子与家庭
home and family...
还有爱情
and love.
人生里值得提及的每一件事
Everything that counts for anything in life...
我都拥有
I have it.
但是梦每次都以同样的方式结束
But the dream ends the same way every time.
我失去了一切
I lose it all.
拉斯维加斯 内华达州
各位 玩的是德州扑克
The game is Texas Hold 'Em, gentlemen.
你带太太来了吗
You bring your wife ?
你以为我来这里玩牌会带我太太来吗
You think I'm sitting here, I bring my wife ?
-蠢货才带他太太来呢  -因为那个人就是我
- Dumb-ass brought his wife. - 'Cause I'm the man.
我说玩牌就是玩牌 与此同时
I say I'm playing poker, I play poker. Meanwhile,
你太太正在普拉诺市跟邮差乱搞呢
your wife is back in Plano boinking the mailman.
嘿 你叫什么名字来着
Hey, what was your name again ?
冯斯顿 斯图尔特·冯斯顿  嗨
Funsten. Stuart Funsten. Hi.
嘿 你带老婆来了
Hey,you bring a little lady, Stuart ?
不 我还没结婚呢
I'm not married.
聪明人
Smart man.
你们每年都来参加吗 国防会议
You guys come to this every year ? Def-Con ?
每年 不要了
Every year. Fold.
-不会错过大会  -是呀 爆了
- Wouldn't miss it. - Yeah. Out.
那么 你们近来有没有搞什么
So,you guys working on anything
有趣的东西
interesting these days ?
老套的暗黑行动的玩意儿 你知道那是什么
Same old black-ops crapola. You know what it's like.
我们在搞有关中子轰炸的事
Hey, we're doing some neat stuff with neutron bombardment.
是啊 你可以煮熟别人的脑袋
Yeah, you can cook somebody's
就像是水煮蛋一样
brain in their skull, like hard-boiling an egg.
它真的很棒
It's neat stuff!
谈到烂东西    不要了
Speaking of crapola Fold.
-谢谢  -喔 您真与众不同
- Thank you. - Oh. A man of distinction.
你要跟进吗 冯斯顿先生
So, you in, Mr. Funsten ?
是的
Yeah.
看来只有你和我了
Looks like it's just you and me.
再加200
Another 200.
我跟你的200
I'll see your 200,
而且再加1000
and raise you 1 ,000.
他全买了 斯图
He's buying the pot, Stu.
外面三张梅花 可能是同花
Three clubs showing. Could be a flush.
跟1000
One thousand,
我再加1000
and I raise you one thousand.
-他一定有好牌 -是呀
- What stones he has ! - Yeah !
我看你是军工集团的
I see you work for Conglomerated.
你们的AE-135很棒
You guys make a great AE-1 3 5 unit.
喔 老兄 别紧张 别紧张
Oh, man, don't freak. Don't freak.
我在查 AE-135
I'm on it. AE-1 3 5.
查找 有了
Searching. Bingo!
442-J-冲程-AE-135
442-J-Stroke-AE-1 3 5.
B2轰炸机的空调系统
Air conditioning units for B-2 bombers.
谈空调系统
Talk air conditioners.
喔 是呀 AE-135美极了
Oh, yeah. The AE-1 3 5's a beauty.
能让B-2保持冰凉
Keeps the B-2s frosty.
你简直看得到呼出来的水气
You can practically see your breath.
你们怎么解决它的毛病的
How'd you get all the bugs out of it ?
啊 你知道 商业机密
Ah, you know trade secrets.
得了吧 斯图尔特 这里都是朋友
Come on, Stuart. You're among friends.
说真的
Seriously,
你们是怎么克服复合材料的层间剥离的
how'd you get past the "Delamination'' thing ?
"层间剥离" 我在找
"Delamination. '' I'm searching.
喔 抱歉 我跟你的1000
Oh, I'm sorry. I'll see your thousand,
还有
and...
加到你的全部
raise you all you've got.
系统检测 当机了 找不到
Systems test. Error rates nothing.
跟他拖时间 别跟了
Stall him and fold !
你们想知道我们是
You want to know how we
怎么解决层间剥离的吗
fixed the "Delamination'' problem ?
我们把整个该死的东西转包给日本人
We subcontracted the whole damn thing to the Japanese,
然后让政府付三倍的帐单
then triple-billed the government.
这是我们的一贯作法
Same thing we always do.
Q打头同花
Queen-high flush.
哇
God!
K打头
King-high.
艾尔 叫保安
Al, call security.
叫他们来抓这位冯斯顿先生 还有他的同伙
Have them pick up Mr. Funsten here and his partner.
"层间剥离" 那是你瞎掰的
"Delamination.'' You made that up.
给你一个建议吧 斯图尔特
My advice to you, Stuart
不管你真名是什么
or whatever your name really is
你都不是玩扑克的料
poker is not your game.
嘿 老兄 你想玩铁笼决斗吗 来呀
Hey, man, you want to thunderdome ? Let's go !
三千美金
Three thousand dollars !
我告诉你别跟了
I told you to fold.
应该是我在里面玩牌
That should have been me in there playing.
为什么要拜尔斯去冒充
Why does Byers get to do the undercover ?
因为这不是伍德斯托克音乐节
'Cause this ain't Woodstock.
我们至少还应该能从
Did we at least get some usable
用过的酒杯上得到有用的指纹吧
prints off the drink glasses ?
什么 你在开玩笑
What ? Are you kidding ?
我不得不把杯子全都留下
I had to leave them all behind.
-我们要怎么挽回损失  -不用了
- How are we gonna salvage this ? - We're not.
这次大会是个失败
This convention's a bust.
投资了五天时间和三千美金
Five days and three grand invested.
结果毫无所获
We've got bubkes to show for it.
那个玩牌的到底是谁
Who was that player, anyway ?
那个耍我们的家伙
The guy who made us.
他没有挂大会的名牌
He wasn't wearing a convention badge.
没人提到他的名字
Nobody ever said his name.
我认为他值得查一查
I think he's worth looking into.
中情局 开门
C.I.A. ! Open up !
嘿 吉米和提米
Hey. Jimmy and Timmy.
嘿 你们今天到哪儿去了
Hey. Where were you guys today ?
在附近
Around.
喔 是吗 也许是
Oh, yeah ? Maybe snooping
在打探热门的411
for some hot 411 ?
用秘密的手段
On the sneak tip ?
-也许  -是吗 也许我们也是
- Maybe. - Yeah, well, maybe we were too.
-也许我们查到点东西  -也许我们也查到了
- And maybe we got some. - Well, maybe we did too.
其实我们没什么收获
Ah, we got bubkes.
真是一群口风很紧的国防厂商
Bunch of tight-lipped defense contractors.
我想我敢冒很大的险说
Yeah, I'm gonna go way
是因为你的T恤衫  注:T恤上写着"懦夫政府"
out on a limb here and say it's the T-shirt.
是啊 也许你们俩
Yeah. Maybe both of you
都该穿一件上面写着"我是傻蛋"的T恤
could wear one that says "I'm with stupid. ''
你就是不懂 老兄
You just don't get it, man.
这是说我们盯上他们了
This says that I'm onto them.
这是说我了解
This says that I comprehend
军方与工业界的互动关系
the military-industrial power dynamic.
这整件事就是这样
That's what this whole thing is about.
非法行动 政治暗杀
Wetworks, political assassination.
这是他们今年的主题
That's their theme for this year.
-你从哪儿听来的  -喔 是呀
- Where did you hear that ? - Oh, yeah.
好像我会泄露消息来源一样  我只能告诉你们
Like I'm gonna reveal my sources. Suffice it to say,
有一些重要的新式隐匿暗杀科技
there's some big, new stealth assassination technology...
会在这里推出
that's supposed to be unveiled here,
而我会在现场 坐在前排
and I will be there, front row.
现在 我们会突击餐厅
In the meantime, we're hitting the restaurant.
-是呀 随便你吃的龙虾大餐  -免费演出
- Yeah, all-you-can-eat lobster buffet. - Free floor show.
会有很多波霸 你们会来吗
Plenty of boobage. You guys down ?
-当然  -你们先去吧
- Sure. - You go ahead.
我随后就到
I'll catch up.
你看起来悲伤极了 拜尔斯
You're one hell of a sad sack,Byers.
不要提扑克牌局
Lay off about the poker game.
不 我说的不是那个
No, that's not what I'm talking about.
你是最积极鼓动我们
You're the one who pushes the
来参加大会的人
hardest for us to come to these conventions,
我们到了之后 你却最古怪
and then you get all squirrely once we get here.
你还在找她 是吗
You're still looking for her, aren't you ?
苏珊·莫德斯基
Susanne Modeski.
我们是在一次大会上遇到她的
We met her at a convention.
那是十年前了 在巴尔的摩
Ten years ago, in Baltimore.
我们都知道她的遭遇
And we both know what happened to her.
她很可能已经死了
Most likely, she's dead.
不 她是个有才华的科学家
No. She was a brilliant
对政府太重要了
scientist too important to the government.
老弟 不论如何 我知道我们都希望
Buddy, either way, I know we're both hoping...
她在比拉斯维加斯更好的地方
she's in a better place than Las Vegas.
来吧 随便你吃的龙虾大餐
Come on. All-you-can-eat lobster.
-我差点就赢了  -是啊 你和其他每个人都一样
- I almost won. - Yeah, you and everyone else.
拜尔斯 试试这个 我感觉运气很好
Byers, check this out. I'm feeling lucky.
-这不可能  -什么
- It can't be. - What ?
对不起 对不起
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
拜尔斯 到底发生了什么事
Byers ! What the hell's going on ?
-是我 史考利  -嗨 史考利 是我
- Yeah, Scully. - Hey, Scully, it's me.
-穆德 现在几点了  -凌晨2:34
- Mulder, what time is it ? - 2:34 a.M.
听着 史考利
Listen, Scully,
我要你搭下一班飞机到拉斯维加斯
I need you on the next flight to Las Vegas.
拉斯维加斯 为什么
Las Vegas ? Why ?
是孤枪侠他们
It's the Lone Gunmen.
他们发现了一些大事
They're on to something big.
到底是什么
What, exactly ?
真的很重要 相信我
It's really important. Trust me.
是的 我相信你 穆德
Yeah, I trust you, Mulder.
我只是不太相信那三个小丑
It's the Three Stooges I'm not so sure about.
听着 我不能在不安全的电话里谈这些
Look, I can't talk over an unsecured line.
拜托一定要来 这是紧急事件
Please just get here. It's an emergency.
好的 好的 好的
Okay. Okay, okay, okay.
万一她打电话给他怎么办
What if she calls him back ?
我锁住了她的手机号码
I trapped her cell number.
如果她打给他 会转到这里的
If she calls him, it rings here.
她准会踢我们屁股的
She's gonna kick our ass.
你究竟需要史考利做什么
What do you need Scully for anyway ?
我们在对抗政府探员
We're up against agents of the government.
我们需要自己的政府探员
We need our own government agent.
那也应该是穆德
And that would be Mulder.
你为什么只找史考利
Why do you want just Scully ?
她会踢我们屁股的
She's gonna kick our ass.
穆德太引人注意了
Mulder's too high-profile.
他的名字对于那些在巴尔的摩
He's virtually a household name...
绑架苏珊的黑衣人来说 简直如雷贯耳
to the black-ops who kidnapped Susanne in Baltimore.
拜尔斯 我已经侵入了饭店的电脑
Byers, I've hacked into the hotel computer.
苏珊·莫德斯基没有在这里登记
Susanne Modeski's not registered here.
你确定你看到她了吗
Are you sure you saw her ?
你绝对肯定是她吗
Are you absolutely, positively sure ?
是她 她在这里 我必须要找到她
It was her. She's here. I've gotta find her.
你必须要找一些冰块 你需要喝一杯
You've gotta find some ice. You need a drink.
你去哪儿了
Where were you ?
只是去玩扑克 浪费时间而已
Just wasting time at a poker game.
拜尔斯正在试图自杀
Byers is trying to kill himself.
别再试图自杀了 拜尔斯
Stop trying to kill yourself, Byers.
桶不够深
It's not deep enough.
来看看这是什么
Come see what we got.
1066房登记的是
Room 1 066. Registered to
我们的神秘扑克手格兰特·艾利斯
our mystery poker player one Grant Ellis.
他的车挂的是新墨西哥的牌照
New Mexico plates on his car.
查询结果显示是国防部的车
Which come back listed D.O.D. Motor pool.
-是在    -白石城 新墨西哥州注册的
- Signed out from - Whitestone, New Mexico.
陆军新式武器研究所
The Advanced Army Weapons Facility,
苏珊以前工作的地方
where Susanne worked.
艾利斯的信用卡帐单
Ellis's credit cards get
直接送到行政办公室
billed directly to the administrative offices.
他看起来像是
He's looking like
某种秘密政府的高官
he's some kind of shadow government pooh-bah.
他给她洗脑了
He brainwashed her.
他们在那里就是干这个勾当
Well, that's what they do there !
她研制出来的E-H气体
The E-H gas she developed.
号称是心理战 行为修正
Call it psychological warfare, behavior modification,
但实际上就是控制心智
but it's all about mind control.
毫无疑问
And undoubtedly
过去十年他们改进了方法
the process has been refined in the last decade.
她逃离了他们 拒绝参加他们的试验
She ran from them. Refused to take part in their tests
那些他们对美国人民犯下的罪行
their crimes against the American people.
她现在不可能自愿
There's no way she would choose to
为他们工作
be working for them now,
为那个家伙工作 亲吻他
working for that guy, kissing him.
很显然 是他给她洗了脑
Clearly, he brainwashed her.
我有办法查出来
I know a way to find out.
[西班牙语]日安
Buenos dias.
我没法儿混进大会
I can't get into the conference.
看门的是那个把我赶出赌场的警卫
The guard who threw me out is working the door.
让我去
Let me go.
中情局 不许动
C.I.A. ! Freeze !
真是越来越好笑了
That just keeps getting funnier.
你的女朋友提米呢
Where's your girlfriend Timmy ?
到沙漠里去了
Out in the desert.
那里有位裸体小姐
There's this naked chick
教你如何使用机关枪
who'll teach you how to shoot machine guns.
但是要花200元 我告诉他他是个色鬼
It costs 200 beans, though. I told him he was a putz.
你怎么了 拜尔斯
What's the matter, Byers ?
你最喜欢的狗死了吗 怎么了
Your bestest dog die ? What's up ?
我们正在想办法
We're trying to figure out
进入大会会场
how to get into the Saguaro Room.
祝你好运 那简直就是圣杯 想用窃听器吗
Good luck ! That's the Holy Grail. Bug sweeps ?
外面有赌场警卫 里面有政府探员
Casino security outside ? Government security inside ?
我们谁都不可能进去
There's no way any of us are getting in.
我能够进去
I can get in there.
只要时机成熟 我就能进去
And I will too, when the time is right.
瞎吹吧 你就
Doo-doo, ca-ca, poo-poo.
去梳你的头发吧 迈克尔·波顿(大明星)
Go brush your hair, Michael Bolton.
他们的保安有漏洞
There's a hole in their security.
我已经全搞懂了
I've got it all figured out.
但是在明天推出新型暗杀科技之前
But there's nothing worth hearing in there until tomorrow,
没什么值得听的
when they unveil their new assassination technology.
还在掰你那些暗杀科技吗
Again with the assassination technology, hmm ?
我必须混进去 吉米
I need to get in there, Jimmy.
我必须知道那里面今天发生了什么
I need to know what's happening in there today.
如果你真能进去 证明给我看
If you can really get in there, prove it.
实际应用永远
Real-world application will always,
永远是武器测试的必要环节
always remain a necessary component of weapons testing.
显然 一件武器不能用于战场
And obviously, a weapon can't be fielded,
不能加入军备
can't be put into the arsenal,
除非它的战斗效能可以确定
until its efficacy in combat can be established.
如果各位愿意
Now, if you'll take a
看一下我们提供的
look at the kill/ratio productivity chart...
杀伤力图表
we've provided for you.
翻到   第22页那里 你们会发现
Turn to On page 22 there, you'll see that
喔 这里有你的法西斯小妞 拜尔斯
Ooh. There's your fascist chickie, Byers.
提米
Timmy ?
糟了
Damn.
不许动 不许动
Hold on ! Hold on !
他妈的怎么回事
What the hell is going on ?
你是他们的人
You're one of them.
你真的把事情搞砸了 吉米
You really screwed things up, Jimmy.
我们本来为你安排了大计划的
We had big plans for you.
什么大计划
What big plans ?
政治暗杀 我是对的
Political assassination. I was right.
我对事件事的看法都是对的
I was right about the whole thing !
每个好计划都需要一个替罪羊
Every good plan needs a patsy.
不要
No !
-请你提着这些行李好吗  -当然
- Can you take these up, please ? - Sure.
-史考利探员  -穆德探员在哪儿
- Agent Scully. - Where's Agent Mulder ?
-我一直在打他的电话  -呃
- I've been trying to call him. - Uh
我想他的电话出了问题
He's, uh I think his phone's messed up.
未来几小时里可能很难联络到他
He may be hard to reach for the next few hours.
他建议我们跟你一起工作 带你进入状况
He suggested we work with you. Bring you up to speed.
当然 带我进入状况吧
By all means, bring me up to speed.
受伤的人是谁
Who's the injured party?
伤者名叫詹姆士·贝尔蒙特 完毕
Subject's name is James Belmont. Over.
-这边  -天啊 是吉米
- This way. - Oh, man. Jimmy.
我们正经过大厅
We're crossing the lobby now.
他被撞了 快看 那边
He got hit ! Look ! Over there !
他突然跳出来 没有预兆 什么都没有
He just jumped. No warning. No nothing.
他突然跳到我车子前面
He just dived right out in front of me.
喔 天啊 是吉米
Oh, God. It is Jimmy.
不是我的错 他本来站在那里
It's not my fault. He was just standing there,
然后他突然就跳到车底下了
and then he just dives under the bus.
-这不是自杀  -你们认识这个人
- This wasn't a suicide. - You know this man ?
这里出了什么事
What's going on here ?
苏珊 你还记得我吗
Susanne. Do you remember me ?
约翰 你在这里作什么
John, what are you doing here ?
-我是来救你的  -救我
- I'm here to save you. - From what ?
我认为你失去了自我
I don't think you are yourself.
我认为 呃 你受到虐待
I think that, uh, you've been mistreated...
被迷惑了
and confused and
恐怕你的信念
I'm afraid that your beliefs,
你的意志已经不再是你自己的了
your opinions are no longer your own.
你是说我被洗脑了吗
As in "I've been brainwashed'' ?
我不知道该怎么给你解释 我没被洗脑
I don't know what to tell you. I haven't been.
你可能会有生命危险 苏珊
Your life may be in danger, Susanne.
我的一位朋友刚刚遇害
A friend of mine has just been killed.
-是被谋杀  -什么
- Murdered. - What ?
-而那个和你在一起的男人    -我的未婚夫
- And that man that you're with - My fiance ?
对不起 约翰 我想你该走了
I'm sorry,John. I-I think you better go.
不 等等 等一下
No, wait, wait.
十年前 我看见你被推进车里
Ten years ago, I saw you thrown into a car.
就在我眼前被绑架
Kidnapped right in front of me.
难道那没有发生过 难道那全是我做的梦吗
Did that not happen ? Did I just dream all of that ?
是发生了
It happened.
但是事态改善了
But things got better.
喔 抱歉 老弟
Whoops. Sorry, buddy.
那个苏珊还真是个受欢迎的女孩
That Susanne's a popular girl.
你真的确定想呆在这里
You're absolutely sure you want to be here for this ?
确定 我很冷静
Oh,yeah.I'm cool.
让我们找出是什么害了他
Let's just find out what killed him.
好吧
Okay.
詹姆斯·贝尔蒙特 29岁
James Belmont. Age 29.
目视检查显示伤势
Visual exam reveals injuries...
符合重大外伤的情况
consistent with massive trauma.
肋骨多处折断 附带出血
Multiple rib fractures with concomitant hemorrhaging,
内部外部都有
both internal and external.
脊椎断裂 而且部分暴露
The spine is fractured and partially exposed.
有没有可能是他们对他做了什么
What if they did something to him,
例如 使他自己惊慌失措
you know, to make him pancake himself?
他们是谁
Who's "They'' ?
你知道的 "他们"
You know, "Them.''
我从胸部解剖开始
I'll begin with the "Y'' incision.
朗格利 你能过去
Langly, will you go over
拿电锯给我吗
there and pass me the Stryker saw, please ?
就在那边的台子上
It's right there on the counter.
谢谢
Thank you.
你没事吧 朗格利
Are you okay, Langly ?
史考利
Scully ?
史考利 醒醒
Scully, wake up.
-你没事吧  -出什么事了
- Are you okay ? - What happened ?
我想是你有点想吐
I'm thinking that you got a little queasy
然后摔到脑袋了
and took a header.
你知道 血和内脏会让一些人难受的
You know, blood and guts can bother some people.
我猜是吧
Yeah. I guess.
你会没事吧
You gonna be all right ?
当然 美人儿
Sure, cutie.
那 你检查完吉米了吗
So, you're done with Jimmy ?
完了 完了 完了
Done, done, done.
这玩意儿是怎么推的
How do you roll this thing ?
呃 史考利
Uh, Scully ?
是什么杀了他
What killed him ?
我的医学意见是
My medical opinion
哔
Beep !
你就只发现这些
And that's all you found ?
就是这些
That's all I know.
史考利
Scully ?
你发现了什么
What did you find out ?
检尸没有结果
Autopsy was negatory.
吉米是自己压死的
Jimmy squished himself.
那个秀色可餐的史考利探员呢
And where is the scrumptious Agent Scully ?
她说她有重要的事要办
She said she had something important to do.
老兄 她的时差还没倒过来呢
Man, she is seriously jet-lagged.
你的装置弄好了吗
You got product already ?
没有 有人捷足先登了
No. An earlier bird got the worm.
总是等待
All this waiting.
我觉得他们在监视我们
I feel like they're keeping tabs on us, watching us.
亲爱的 你担心太多了
Honey,you worry too much.
计划仍然依照进度
The plan is still on schedule.
船到桥头自然直
Everything's falling into place.
我们为这件事努力了这么久
We've worked so long and so hard for this.
这不是她的本性
It's not her.
是他们迫使她的 用某种方法
They're making her do this somehow.
老弟
Buddy, now,
我对女人略知一二 相信我
I know something about the fairer sex, trust me.
你可以牵马到河边
You can bring a horse to water,
可是你无法让她喝水
but you can't make her drink.
她不会跟那个人结婚的
She would not marry that man.
你不像我这么了解他
You don't know him like I do.
你怎么进来的
How'd you get in here ?
你们中的一个把这个掉在我房里了
One of you left this in my room.
格兰特·艾利斯救了我一命
Grant Ellis saved my life.
他救了成千上万条人命
He saved the lives of thousands.
我必须和你谈谈 约翰
I need to talk to you,John.
我必须试着解释这一切
I need to try and explain everything.
来吧 我们去玩几把
Come on. Let's hit the slots.
小心背后
Watch your back.
马塔·哈瑞注:一战时德国著名的女间谍
Mata Hari.
你提到你的朋友遇害的事
You said something about a friend being murdered.
我无法证明
Not that I can prove it.
但是我认为他
But I think he saw something
在你们的大会上看到了不该看的事
he was not supposed to see at your conference.
-你可能身处险境  -我知道 一直都是
- You may be in danger. - I am always.
格兰特也是
So is Grant.
这一刻我想像过许多次
I have thought about this moment so many times.
如果我再次遇到你 我会说些什么话
All the things I would say to you if I ever saw you again.
然后你就出现在我门口
And then there you were at my door,
而我
and I
十年前他们抓走我
They took me ten years ago.
他们对我作了些事
They did things to me.
每天都像是在溺水
And it was like drowning every day underwater,
挣扎着呼吸
struggling to breathe.
有一天 一只手穿过水面
And one day a hand broke the surface,
伸下来拉我出来
reached down and pulled me up.
我本来希望是你 约翰
I wanted it to be you,John.
但那是格兰特
It was Grant.
他为他们工作 为那个计划
He worked for them the project.
我以前不信任他 好几年都不信任
I didn't trust him, not for years,
直到我意识到
not until I realized that
他是以他自己的方式对抗他们
he was working against them in his own way.
拖延他们 破坏他们的试验
Stalling them, sabotaging their tests.
他使我想起了你
He reminded me of you.
-我有良心可是你的幸运  -怎么说
- They're just lucky I got a conscience. - How's that ?
如果我对赌场施展我真正的功夫
If I unleash my true kung fu on this casino,
我在一周之内就能让银行破产了
I could break the bank within a week.
是啊 你会发现自己被埋在沙漠底下六英尺深的
Yeah, and find yourself buried under six feet of desert dirt.
-嘿 伙计们  -嘿 提米
- Hey, guys. - Hey, Timmy.
我们都为吉米感到难过
I'm sorry aboutJimmy.
嘿 朗格利
Hey, Langly ?
大家都在我的房间
The guys are all up in my
为纪念吉米
room for a round of Dungeons and Dragons...
举行龙与地下城游戏大赛
in honor ofJimmy.
曼汉姆爵爷会出席的  注:Lord Manhammer 龙与地下城中的人物
Lord Manhammer will be in attendance.
我要去玩点游戏纪念一下
I'm gonna go play a little D&D in memoriam.
这可真感人 老兄
That's touching, man.
你喜欢顶层公寓吗
You like penthouses ?
-史考利  -喔
- Scully ? - Oh !
嘿 希基 好久不见
Hey, Hickey. Long time no see.
不 那不好 我喜欢希基
No, that's not nice. I like Hickey.
抽烟吗
Cigarette ?
你不吸烟的
You don't smoke.
谁有火柴
But who's got a match ?
喔
Well...
我都无法决定让谁点燃我的火好了
I just can't decide who lights my fire.
够了 行了 各位大众情人 滚开
That's it. All right, you dandies, back off.
这是调查局的丹娜·史考利探员
This is Special Agent Dana Scully of the F.B.I.
只要敢碰她一根汗毛
If you so much as touch her,
就可能触犯联邦法律
you may be committing a federal offense.
走吧 走吧
Come on. Come on.
我们本来可以罗曼蒂克一番的
We could have been stardust.
下次再说吧
Maybe next time.
喔
Ooh.
希望你带了皮夹
I hope you brought your wallet,
朋友 要不是因为这是追悼大会
my friend. Just because this is a memorial game
这算什么
What's this ?
喔 我们给你安排了一个游戏
Oh, we have got a game for you.
相信我 这会成功的
Trust me. This is gonna work.
-这不是你录的  -不是
- You didn't tape this ? - No.
这意味着他们在监视我们
Which means they surveilled us.
他们知道我们的计划 他们知道所有的事
They know our plans. They know everything.
-你们的计划是什么  -逃走
- What is your plan ? - To escape.
这个大会是我们的机会
This conference was our chance
在最后一天溜走
to slip out on the last day
公开我们的档案
go public with our files,
公开所有的武器研究计划
all our weapons research.
我们这次终于能够成功
We could finally make it happen this time.
我们已经收集了足够的证据
We'd gathered up enough proof.
公众从没像现在这样接近真相
The public is ready to believe now more than ever.
他们知道了一切
They know everything.
他们会杀掉我们 约翰-格兰特和我
They'll kill us,John Grant and me both.
-嗨 -来吧 来吧
- Hi ! - Come on. Come on.
过来 静下来 静下来
Come on. Settle down. Settle down.
好的 好的
Okay, okay, okay.
我在酒吧发现史考利探员正在招蜂引蝶
I found Agent Scully Go-Lightly holding court in the bar.
我从没见过她喝醉酒
I've never seen her drunk before.
天啊 这不可能
God. This can't be.
-嗨 -劳驾
- Hi. - Please.
她不是喝醉 看看这个
She's not drunk. Look at this.
这是注射造成的
That was made by an injector gun.
她被注射了什么鬼东西
What the hell was she injected with ?
一种E-H气体的衍生物
It's a derivative of E-H gas.
A-H 精神组胺 我最新的发明
A-H. Anoetic histamine. My latest creation.
我几年前就能够研发出来的
I could have developed it years ago,
只是被我拖延了
but I held off.
我不想让那些
I wasn't about to let those
差使我的混蛋们拥有它
bastards I work for get their hands on it.
格兰特认为
Grant thought that
如果我们秘密研发出一小批
if we secretly developed a small batch...
然后再销毁记录
and then destroyed the notes,
我们就有了对大众公开的证据
we would have the proof we needed to go public.
我们也就有了可以对付他们的武器
We'd also have a weapon we could use against them.
还有谁能拿到这些精神组胺
Who else has access to this anoetic histamine ?
只有格兰特和我两个人
Grant and I are the only two people that have
才拥有样品
that have the samples.
这会抵消药物的作用
This will counteract the anoetic effect.
嘿 美人儿
Hey, cutie.
噢
Ow !
只是小小一枝针
Just a little prick.
-严重幻觉  -她会没事的
- Bad trip ? - She'll be fine.
她睡一会儿就会好了
She just needs to sleep it off.
我不懂
I don't understand.
为什么政府要
Why would the government want to
把史考利变成个荡妇
turn Scully into a bimbo ?
那只是潜在的副作用
That's just a potential side effect.
精神组胺会阻碍较高级的大脑功能
Anoetic histamine impedes higher brain functions.
使人容易受到暗示的影响
It promotes suggestibility.
控制心智 洗脑
Mind control. Brainwashing.
这就解释了吉米的事 是他们叫他去自杀的
That explains Jimmy. They told him to commit suicide.
还有史考利 他们使她忘记验尸结果
And Scully. They made her forget her autopsy findings.
但是他们更大的目的是什么
But what is their larger purpose ?
他们在计划什么
What are they planning ?
不论它是什么 我们最好快点找出来
Well, whatever it is, we better find out fast.
真准时
Right on time.
这是你的武器
This is your weapon.
你要做的只是扣动扳机
All you do is pull the trigger.
你应该在上午10:05进入会场
You will enter the Saguaro Room at 1 0:05 a.M.
这个证件让你能够通行
This badge will give you access.
坐在后排的椅子上等着
Take a seat toward the back and wait.
在10:15会宣布休息
1 5, a break will be called.
起身 接近目标
Rise, approach the target,
然后连开三枪
and fire three shots.
这就要谈到可接受风险的问题了
This brings us to the notion of acceptable risk.
当然 风险的定义是
Of course, risk is defined as exposure...
在试用期间与事后评估中暴露于药物
during both utilization and post-project evaluation.
现在 在保密的试验场
Now, in a secure proving ground,
也就是国内试验中
i.E., a domestic engagement,
我们获得了很大成功
we have had great success.
而在国外的试用
Now, offshore utilizations...
可以提供一个可接受风险的
can afford a more comprehensive definition...
更全面的定义
of acceptable risk.
适当的目标评估可以提供
Proper target appraisal can provide...
一个无风险的试用环境
a risk-free trial environment.
一个综合了政治动荡
A combination of political
和无基建基础的环境
instability and lack of efficient infrastructure...
也可以提供一个
can offer a target area of nearly...
几乎无潜在风险的目标区
zero risk-potential.
-经过授权才可以进入  -我是联邦调查局探员
- Authorized attendees only. - I'm an F.B.I. Agent.
授权才能进入
Authorized attendees.
当然 风险管理是与
Of course, risk management goes hand in hand...
行动准备的妥当度并行的
with operational preparedness.
我们剩下的时间
That happens to be our
-刚好要谈到那个主题  -艾尔
-topic for the remainder of this session. - Al ?
呃
Huh ?
我想现在是休息的好时机
I think this would be a good time to take a break.
-可以吗  -喔 当然
- Shall we ? - Oh. Yeah.
休息五分钟 各位 有烟就抽吧
Let's take five, everybody. Smoke 'em if you got 'em.
喔 我的上帝
Oh, my God.
快来人救救她
- - Somebody help her!
-苏珊  -联邦探员
- Susanne. - Federal agent.
打电话呼救
Call for help.
我们在仙人掌厅
We're in the Saguaro Room.
我们需要救护车 有位女士中弹了
We need an ambulance. A woman's been shot.
-她在流血 快点 -我们就来
- She's bleeding. Hurry. - We're on our way.
是谁干的 是谁干的
Who did this ? Who did this ?
开枪的人逃跑了
The shooter got away.
看着这个人 把他带走
Detain this man. Get him out of here.
走吧
Let's go.
干得好 邦德女郎
Good work, party girl.
我会带你去的
I'll take him from here.
等一下 你要带我去哪里
Wait a minute. Where are you taking me ?
苏珊
Susanne ?
我们可以独处一会儿吗
Could we have a moment alone, please ?
-我不会有事的  -我们就在外面
- I'll be fine. - We'll be right down the hall.
好的
Okay.
谢谢你的小费
Thanks for the tip.
大吃一惊 是不是
Big surprise, huh ?
因为你设计我的朋友来杀我
Since you programmed my friend to kill me ?
不 苏珊 那不是我的主意
No, Susanne. It wasn't my idea.
你知道这件事
You knew about it.
你把药物给了他们 A-H
You gave it to them the A-H.
如果我没想到检查朗格利
If I hadn't thought to check Langly
如果我没有给他解药
If I hadn't given him the antidote
我不明白
I don't understand.
当初为什么要救我
Why save me ?
为什么救我一命只是为了要杀掉我
Why save my life just to take it away ?
你知道原因
You know why.
你已经不需要我了 你得到了你想要的
You were done with me. You had what you wanted.
是他们得到了他们想要的
They had what they wanted.
研究计划结束了
The project was over.
我对天发誓 这不是我的主意
Honest to God, it wasn't my idea.
你花那么多年骗取我的信任
All those years you spent gaining my trust.
假装你爱我
You pretended that you loved me.
他们能给你什么报酬
What could they possibly give you for that ?
你这样做值得吗 格兰特
What was it worth to you, Grant ?
你的价钱是多少 你得到了什么
What was your price ? What did you get ?
性命 不然他们会杀掉我
My life. They'd kill me.
哈啰
Hello.
我很抱歉 苏珊
I'm so sorry, Susanne.
先是郡里的死亡记录
The county death records first.
然后是州的缴税名单 快点
Then the state tax rolls. Come on.
再下来是克拉克郡停尸间
Then the Clark County Morgue.
列出他们搞错的尸体
List they misplaced the body.
为什么你不用你那娘娘腔的玩意儿射我
Why don't you just zap me with
然后再洗我的脑呢
your girlie's thing there and brainwash me again ?
我说下手吧 然后我们就让他剪头发了
I say do it. Then we can make him cut his hair.
你去开门好吗
Will you answer that ?
为什么是我 她是你的小妞
Why me ? She's your little chickadee.
快点 别闹了
Hurry up. Come on.
进来吧 马塔·哈瑞
Come on in, Mata Hari.
中情局 不许动
C.I.A. Freeze.
-放她走  -才怪
- Let her go. - Sure.
不要
No !
你知道杀掉你们三个最大的好处是什么
You know the best thing about killing you three ?
我以后不必再穿的跟你们一样了
- I won't have to dress like you anymore. -
把他拖走
Get him off me.
嗨 美人儿
Hi, cutie.
你要怎么处置他
What do you want to do with him ?
警方证实已经逮捕一个
Police confirm an arrest has been made.
这个人 新墨西哥州 阿拉莫戈多的蒂莫西·朗道
This man Timothy Landau of Alamogordo, New Mexico
已经招供谋杀格兰特·艾利斯
has confessed to the murders of Grant Ellis
以及苏珊·莫德斯基
and Susanne Modeski.
喂 穆德
Hello ? Mulder ?
你听得到吗
Can you hear me ?
我在酒店 你在哪儿
I'm at the hotel. Where are you ?
你说"什么酒店"是什么意思 拉斯维加斯呀
What do you mean, "What hotel'' ? Las Vegas.
我在拉斯维加斯 你不在吗
I'm in Las Vegas. Aren't you ?
你打电话给我的
You called me.
你说没打电话给我是什么意思
What do you mean, you didn't call me ?
喔 见鬼 我要踢他们的屁股
Oh, man. I am gonna kick their asses.
苏珊·莫德斯基死了
Susanne Modeski is dead.
每个郡 州
Every computer at every county,
联邦机构的每台电脑都知道了
state and federal office knows it.
你现在起就是她
This is who you are now.
跟我一起走
Come with me.
没有我你会更安全的
You'll be safer without me.
没有差别 我告诉过你 我要公开
Doesn't make a difference. I told you, I'm going public.
不 你不该公开
No, you're not.
你做的已经够多了 剩下的交给我们吧
You've done more than enough. Leave it to us now.
那是我们该做的
It's what we do.
本来是要给格兰特的
This was meant for Grant.
我想要你收下它
I want you to have it.
会有那么一天的
Someday.
要去玩几把吗
So, you want to hit the slots ?
知道吗 拜尔斯 和你一起变老 不算是太坏的事
You know, Byers, growing old with us ain't so bad.
喔 闭嘴 朗格利 你真想让他自杀吗
Oh, shut up, Langly. Do you really want him to kill himself?
你们有二角五分的硬币吗
Got any quarters ?